(Amy:)I'm sorry you got stuck with me.
(Amy:)I bet you wanted
to be with Bernadette.
(Howard:)Have you ever played
a game with Bernadette?
(Raj:)-No.
-Have you ever gone
(Howard:)into a steel cage with a wolverine?
(Bernadette:)Faster, faster, faster!
Do you not know that word?
-It means "more fast"!
-Stop yelling at me.
Hey! You'll know
when I'm yelling at you.
Oh. Oh, it's the comic book store!
All right, come on.
(Penny:)That's where we have to go.
(Sheldon:)But we haven't finished the puzzle.
Well, it doesn't matter!
We know the answer!
(Sheldon:)You think you know the answer.
But it could be a trick.
(Sheldon:)What if when the puzzle's complete,
(Sheldon:)there's a sign
in the window that says,
"Go to the train store"?
(Penny:)Okay, it's not gonna say that.
(Sheldon:)Well, I hope you're wrong.
I really want to go to the train store.
It's the comic book store. Let's go!
(Bernadette:)Come on, numb nuts,
it's the comic book store!